VLADIMIR ESTEVEZ

4510 Rue Cayer, Sherbrooke (819) 640-9197 estevez.vladimir@yahoo.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

Computer science technician with 3 years of experience in customer service, e-commerce, and social media management. Seeking a full-time IT role where my technical expertise, extensive computer knowledge, and commitment to continuous learning will meet the needs of both customers and the company.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Strong communication, decision-making and organizational skills.
- Can work in a fast-paced environment.
- · Team oriented
- Able to remain calm during stressful situations
- Autonomous, professional and detailoriented.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Written and spoken languages: English, Spanish and French
- Computer Skills: Microsoft Office, Social Media Management, Web Design (HTML, CSS, React), Programming (C#, JAVA, Python), Database Management (SQL, MongoDB).
- Computer Troubleshooting and Repairing (Hardware and Software).

WORK EXPERIENCE

Service Desk Level I Agent - Global Excel Lennoxville, Québec

2024

- · Prioritized and resolved JIRA tickets.
- Supported computer and mobile device users.
- Delivered rapid solutions for minimal downtime, ensuring continuous workflow.

Technical support at the University of Sherbrooke - Faculty of Medicine CHUS Fleurimont, Sherbrooke, Québec

Summer 2023

- Answer calls from users.
- · Provide solutions related to their computing devices
- Management of databases when updating certain software.

Content Creator and Translator

2022

Tech Quiero, Sherbrooke, Quebec

- Create, translate and edit content on different social media platforms such as (Facebook, Instagram, LinkedIn).
- Provide support to the different social media marketing campaigns.
- · Contribute with bringing a new community to life that promotes women empowering.

Online Sales Representative

GNC Live Well, Buenos Aires, Argentina

- In charge of Customer Service and Product Reviews/Feedbacks.
- Inventory management
- Conducted research to address shipping errors and packaging mistakes

Inventory Manager Assistant

2017-2018

2018 - 2019

Tienda 326, Buenos Aires, Argentina

- Collaborated with purchasing and production to maintain levels of quality and on-hand inventory.
- Handled day-to-day shipping and receiving overseeing more than 20 packages per day.
- Researched and Upgraded the inventory Software to a more sophisticated one

EDUCATION

Computer Science Technology Champlain College, Lennoxville	2021 - 2024
Full Stack Web Development Course Digital House, Buenos Aires, Argentina	2015 - 2016
Pure and applied Sciences Cegep de Sherbrooke, Sherbrooke	2008 - 2011

CERTIFICATES

R&D Programs Certificate - Al Project Blueprint

Summer 2023

Dawson College, Montreal

Data Journalism Challenge - Technical and People's Choice Award

Winter 2023

Dawson College, Montreal

R&D Programs Certificate - Al Winter Cohort

Dawson College, Montreal

Winter 2023

COMMUNITY ENGAGEMENT

- External Vice President at Champlain Student's Association
- Member of Champlain's WUSC Committee which helps sponsors refugee students feel welcomed on their arrival Canada.
- Member of different Student Clubs regarding Mental Health Awareness, Climate Change and Political Discussion.
- · Forces Avenir Awards:
 - Student Perseverance 2022 (Estrie)
 - Finalist Committed Student 2023 (Québec)
- Volunteer at FreeGo Communautaire which provides food from local supermarkets to a community fridge for people in need.